[{"answer": "It depends on, you know, who you're talking to.", "docId": "130930pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "But, Wolf, let me -- does Congress realize just how ridiculous it appears to the rest of the world?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "The Republicans by all accounts are being blamed more than the Democrats from this including in our brand new CNN poll that just came out today.", "docId": "130930pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "Is this just as John McCain said to me, the same movie being replayed?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "Who's to blame, we're going to see what happens and whether or not that the reality matches the polls beforehand and the fear among Republicans frankly that they are the ones who are going to get the blames.", "docId": "130930pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "Who's to blame, how long will it last?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "Well, we have that video that the President delivered to the military that apparently went out to Armed Forces around the world and an interesting juxtaposition there, Piers, as you're seeing, Congress wrangling with each other and arguing and fighting over whether to fund the government for another six weeks and this whole notion of defunding or delaying ObamaCare.", "docId": "130930pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "Jim Acosta, down the White House, have we heard anything from the White House of the President other than the video we saw that he gave to the military?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "Well, I plead with my colleagues who really should just go to the floor and let 218 members of the House of Representatives, not only 218 Republicans decide what legislation we are going to send to the Senate and then to the President.", "docId": "130930pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "Debbie, how do you plead?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "Well, they're not talking because the only thing the Republicans are willing to talk about is whether or not we are to going to delay or defund or repeal ObamaCare.", "docId": "130930pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "Why aren't they talking?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "Look, President Obama has made it very clear that as we implement ObamaCare, which is going to happen, this is a settled matter.", "docId": "130930pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "Isn't not the way any business gets done?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "No, this is the great challenge of this, Piers.", "docId": "130930pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "James Lanksford are you proud of what the Republicans have done tonight?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "No, I'm not happy about it.", "docId": "130930pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "Are you happy about the shut down tonight?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "Well, ObamaCare was of course debated vigorously.", "docId": "130930pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "We need to have this discussion and if it's so great, what are they afraid of?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "... the election was about ObamaCare...", "docId": "130930pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "Amy, you may not like it but it's called -- Amy?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130930pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "Is it exactly the same story replayed now 17 years later?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "Well, I think that's part of it.", "docId": "130930pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "And without that, how do you get anything done?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130930pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "Well, the point I want to make here, is are we dealing though with essentially two quite weak leaders here?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "Well, I think we can again.", "docId": "130930pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "You're the man to us, will we?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "I think you're being overly optimistic Josh.", "docId": "130930pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "I think he's jumping in there, Ryan?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Look, I think John McCain's are on their way out and that's the reason why they weren't able to win the presidential election.", "docId": "130930pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "Who is that should be given (ph) an election who manages to please everybody?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130930pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "In all your years, David, in all your experience and all the Congresses you've seen the Senates you've seen and so on, when you put it all together, have you ever known it as bad as this, the actual polarizing between the two camps?", "qSentId": 554}]